reload.in 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Reload.in

### Privacy Policy 

In the present scenario of an intensely competitive market and constantly evolving technology and products, the abiding central focus continues to be the customer. Excellence in customer service is the most important tool for sustained business growth. Reload.in has attached highest priority to customer satisfaction. 

As a service organization, customer service and customer satisfaction are the prime concerns of Reload.in. When there is a mismatch between the expectation of the customer and the service delivered, it results in dissatisfaction and may lead to complaints. Customer complaints therefore, lead to important and reliable checks on the quality of our services, systems and procedures. 

We committed to maintain and protect your privacy. This policy aims to explain you what information we require, how it is protected, how we use it and with whom it is shared in order to provide you an effective and satisfactory service. By using our service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

### Information Required by Us

We collect only limited personal information from the new user that is necessary for us to provide you the efficient and satisfactory service. 

### Personal information and data about the user collected by us are:

**At the time of registration:** At the time of registration, we collect and store your E-mail address and cell phone number as provided by you in our database. At the time of payment: We do not store the Delivery/Shipping address (Name, Address, City, State, Country and Postal code) and Phone Number at the time you make a payment towards your balance. We don't store any credit card information of the user. At the time of payment, user is redirected to the third-party website where user is required to provide the credit card details. Reload.in does not have any control of the information on the third-party website and does not take any responsibility for the misuse of the credit card information provided by the user to the third party. At Reload.in, we assure to protect your information and will not be distributed to any third party unless you explicitly consent to sharing this information. 

### Use of Information collected

Reload.in uses the collected information to provide you the user friendly, efficient, smooth and satisfactory service. We further use this information, to respond to your suggestions, feedback, and disputes if any and enforce Terms and Conditions of Service agreement. The information provided by you is used for following purposes: 

#### Email

We use the email address provided by you: 

As a unique identifier or login id that helps us to identify your details for processing any information in relation with your account. 

Contacting user in case of any account or payment related need

Participation in any promotional campaign or content organized by us

Processing request for subscription and/or un subscription for e-newsletter

#### Password

You are required to use password or security code with the provided login id to logon to our service in secured mode. As per Terms and Conditions of Service agreement, you are solely responsible to keep this password confidential and for all activities originated from the misuse of the password. Please change your password at regular internals to maintain its confidentiality. 

#### Name

This information allows us to address you in dignified and respectful manner. 

#### Delivery/Shipping Address

The addresses are used to deliver the orders at the specified location in stipulated time and these addresses are further stored in your address book in our database for future use. 

#### Phone Number

We use your phone number to keep you updated with your Reload.in balance, sending you sms for new prepaid plans or vouchers, confirming your authenticity and updating you with latest news on Reload.in 

#### Credit Card Information

We don't store any credit card information of the user. At the time of payment while placing an order, user is redirected to the third-party website where user is required to provide the credit card details. Reload.in does not have any control of the information on the third-party website and does not take any responsibility for the misuse of the credit card information provided by the user to the third party. 

#### Sharing of Information

Reload.in may share provided Personal Information with carefully screened third-party service providers for the sole purpose of providing you with the products, services and information you have requested. Examples of such third-party service providers are credit card authorization companies, mobile operators and targeted advertisers. Reload.in assures you that they do not store, retain or access your information except to provide our services to you and not for any other purpose. 

#### Keeping you informed

Reload.in keeps you informed about new features, products and promotions via email. From time to time, you may receive information on carefully screened third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you. 

#### Changes and Modification

Reload.in reserves the right to modify the Privacy Policy at any time. If our privacy policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site and we will change the 'updated' date at the bottom of this page to reflect the date of the modification. Please visit this page regularly to see the changes if any. 

#### Laws and Regulations

Reload.in may be required by law to disclose your Personal Information to proper law enforcement agencies; even if you requested that we don't share your information. This information may be necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone who committed any offence as per stated laws and regulations. 

#### Merger, Acquisition and Termination of Service

If we merge with, or are acquired by another company, the resulting combined company will use the Personal Information you have provided as described in this policy. If we cease operation, your Personal Information may be transferred to and used by another company that offers similar or related products or services. 

#### Contact Us

Reload.in will do its best to keep your entire information private, and to guard your privacy by continuously evaluating the enforcement of our policies stipulated in this Privacy Policy. Please contact us in any of the following cases: 

If any of your personal information changes or you identify a mistake in our records. If you feel that we are not abiding by our stipulated privacy policy. We will do our best to resolve your inquiry as soon as possible.
